{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_H._Adams_(New_York_politician)",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Coxsackie,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9334778189659119,
            "question": "What was the significance of Coxsackie, New York, to Charles H. Adams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8719552755355835,
            "question": "Where was Charles H. Adams born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8340721130371094,
            "question": "In what state was Charles H. Adams born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7579416036605835,
            "question": "Did Charles H. Adams live in other places besides Coxsackie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6395784020423889,
            "question": "What is the history of Coxsackie, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6002073287963867,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Coxsackie, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941218137741089,
            "question": "What is Charles H. Adams known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4569437503814697,
            "question": "Is there any information about Charles H. Adams's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4532754719257355,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Charles H. Adams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38973239064216614,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Charles H. Adams?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3318_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Charles H. Adams?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3318_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Charles H. Adams's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3318_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Charles H. Adams known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3318_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3318_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention Charles Henry Adams being born in Coxsackie, New York (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3318/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York.\" Specifically, both `16.txt` and `6.txt` mention his birthplace as Coxsackie, Greene County, N.Y., which confirms he was born in Coxsackie, New York."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}